Thank you, Mr. President.
Thank you.
Good evening.
Let us pray.
Almighty God, our Heavenly Father,
send down upon those who hold office in this city of
Myema, the spirit of wisdom, charity, and justice that
with steadfast purpose, they may faithfully serve in their
office to promote the well-being of all people through
Jesus Christ our Lord.
Amen.
Let's pray for the spirit of the world of the world.
I believe in God.
And to the Republic for which stands.
One nation, under God, and the leaders of the world,
who are living in justice for our all.
Who are both going to put out schedule personal
experiences of claims list?
I'll be there.
The next meeting.
Next.
Thank you.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
A minute for the March 18, 2024 meeting.
Thank you.
Hi.
Seven.
Génel Stratton Edmunds, a bomber client for civil litigation,
and amount of 15,560, and 48 cents.
Oh, yes.
Council on board.
This is for expert review, report key for
not-can-new.
This special master.
This is from 3, 6, 2023,
to 22, 2024.
If you remember, back in September,
second of 2008, the council approved
$300,000 for civil litigation costs,
involved in GRDA.
So the current balance is 39,899,996.
If this claim is approved,
$250,648.
That will be the council's $24,390,420.
And this is for the civil litigation.
Thank you.
Hi.
I'm staying.
Okay.
A new business of any of which is written,
since the post office of Inda,
nine staff reports.
10 custody community announcements.
11 adjournments.
Thank you.